I don't
so what else could you do with it
possibility marked out the cleanup the
board regarding the container now what
are you enduring that water what good is
that water could be could be
possibilities that could be
possibilities for you using some other
situations it could be the depot
that water to that rusty oh my god a
possibility that would stop its stop
it's from normal reaction because that
water is carrying a child you different
by charging with that ultimate you know
you just think of things and then to do
those things you would probably have to
play so that's I believe I played his
event his research fine
well yeah cut it up and run into and
think or just once and many things
searching the world yeah you're not
restricted to just trying around a gun
no so now if anybody gets his tape and
he said I know he's gonna put it out
he's no give me anything as such that I
asked for right
and he hasn't offered anything but he's
an agreement right there is none I open
email never asked
take to receive and if I do then that's
great it doesn't matter though I'm not
expecting
that's a bit say but it comes the coach
if anybody out there
I'm just here anybody out there wants to
actually throw some money or Peter and
brains and all that
let's rather thing one thing you can't
do is start of the mate because why help
not interested in no kind of doing
running clothes
the reason I'm just doing this for a
freebie said alright sure
so in their business that is Galgani no
it's not hopefully he's gotta try and do
things by 3:15 to things by free maybe
somebody who wants to throw something
won't be good thing to assist him in
there he'll share he'll pass it on you
know well again so if anybody wants to
throw something at him in his business
then through dunya's you're be assisting
in some way
but I'm not in it I'm not in this group
yeah any questions
yeah sure chef lunch movie yeah she's
got to be quick you go to poverty still
looking out for those monster but he
showed me the last time you just one
come on don't dislike one question
careful here we want to hear where did
you come from
yeah we've Western Australia
yep I'm pretty there was something but
attractive
these are everybody out there I'm not
saying that everything is wrong okay
that the government's and the scientists
and there he goes
I'll shoot them down they have found
some really good stuff and it's stuff
that they're playing with woods
sometimes I'd always use the base colony
stuffing that we can't help that that's
up to them all right honey something you
know she's coming
whatever so they're not always keep
going on on what they call them or
doesn't stop at that you know there's
all those things that they don't want
you to know that really goes in such I
don't like playing so they don't tell
you so you think that memories I brought
it up as a lure it's not with them all
is particles when I know
and he's paid at everybody else's
somebody takes witches
they say
so and then use water for that to
actually assist help where you can
because a lot of the stuff we use
detector to stand on electricity got
Hiller's that's to pay them
educator united transforms today see
am i radiation future
statue up
QG is attention
multiples have wrong advantage
so your
mechanical aging destroyed what is that
mean - Christ fatal some people I think
that power they think about Mexico
humming the morning
for Washington nation no sorry that's
right
it is great comes before every single
thing else everything except they run
cowards are with God my bird Elia stands
with me
we Burt going comes first in there in
second with me I believe it comes out
way too but then once you tell your wife
you keep saying they like to run pretty
early on
it's called chicken
we're studying that
yeah so what attracted you what is the
intention for the work order to count
this finally happened to you and you're
asked a question did you know that your
face guys ready return your energy and
aura guys read every time you're asked a
question
you feel it yeah I see just the
questions worried
there was an attraction
well a sarong would
but it's that concept
God within that club near the fan
there's only one thing all day there's a
mystery
and every single thing I've ever looked
at for something one thing I'll ever
really put to the test in fan
illustrator and that was a gift from God
forgives aggressor Ivan that the old
free energies is not for you
sorry something about
kakashi - Angie
a beautiful silence
I'm not being the paranoid you need to
get us a cool coach to you live cool
cost you a head with a lot of sorta took
five free energy because you have a lot
of money and time and everything else to
actually get it sucks really not free
because free is help give it back it's
not a bottle of paint like the gallon
Cola for you but it's still plus it
means I can say the greatest help me in
get within this will be great so it's
really not free even for him he has to
pay grant has to pay this time added in
life your family yes I'm free